A Finding Aid to the Hiram Powers Papers, 1819-1953, bulk 1835-1883, in the Archives of American Art AAA.powehira
Archives of American Art
- Correspondence, 1819-1883; Series 2; (Box 1-10; 9.0 linear feet)
  - Collie, George, circa 1864-1865 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Cook, Zebedee, 1850 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Coote, Charles, 1845-1848 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Corbin, D. P., 1851 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Crawford, Thomas, 1843-1849 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Cusack, Sophia, circa 1859-1866 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - C, Miscellaneous: Cae-Cam, 1846-1863 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Caesar, G.
    Calhoun, John C.
    Callamore, Gilman
    Cambi, Segritario
    Cameron, E. S.
    Campbell, Donald
    Campbell, Duncan
    Campbell, J. Barnwell
    Campbell, Lewis D.
    Campbell, William
  - C, Miscellaneous: Can-Cas, 1838-1863 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Cannicci, Sevuo[?] G.
    Carlisle, J. E.
    Carlisle, Sarah B.
    Carlton, William T.
    Carr, D. S.
    Carr, Mary E.
    Carruth[?], Mrs. S. A.
    Carter, R. B.
    Cary, E. L.
    Casarette, Peter
    Cass, L. W.
    Casselli[?], Mr.
  - C, Miscellaneous: Ch, 1840-1869 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Chambers, Henrietta R.
    Chambers, William B.
    Chapin, William C.
    Chapman, J. G.
    Chase, Salmon P.
    Cheney, T. A.
    Chickey & Garey
    Child, F. J.
    Childs, George W.
    Chilton, R. S.
    Churchill, Joseph
  - C, Miscellaneous: Cl, 1841-1867 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Claghorn, James L.
    Clapp, Otis
    Clark, M. Lewis
    Clark, Mr.
    Clarke, Ashur
    Clarke, N. George
    Cleanthe, Stamarti
    Clifden, Lord
    Clodan, J. G.
  - C, Miscellaneous: Coa-Com, 1845-1869 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Coale, George B.
    Cogswell, J. G.
    Cohen, J. H.
    Colby, M.
    Cole, Josiah
    Collenet & Atherton
    Collie, James
    Colomb, A.
    Colt, Elisha
    Colt, Sam
    Colton-Salter, G. H.
    Commission of the Cemetery of the Reformed Evangelic Church, Florence
    Commissioner of Patents
  - C, Miscellaneous: Con-Coz, 1843-1873 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Conner, H. W.
    Converse, Julius
    Cook, Zebedee
    Coolidge, Joseph
    Coombs, Margaret L.
    Corcoran, William W.
    Corry, William M.
    Cornish, William
    Costoli, Aritodemo[?]
    Covington, Albert
    Cox, L. L.
    Coxe, Robert E.
    Cozzens, Frederick
  - C, Miscellaneous: Cr, 1836-1871 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Crafts, G. I.
    Cranch, W.
    Crosby, H. G.
    Crosland, Camilla
    Crowell, Eugene
    Croxell, D. C.
  - C, Miscellaneous: Cu, 1838-1866 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Cummings, Thomas S.
    Cunliffe, John
    Currie, C. George
    Cusack, H.
    Cutting, Sewall S.
  - Dangar, Henry C., 1866-1869 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Davis, Brooks & Co., 1849-1853; (2 folders) (Box 3, Folder 10-11)
  - Dehon, Theodore, 1853-1860; (4 folders) (Box 3, Folder 12-15)
  - Dehon, Theodore, 1861-1866; (3 folders) (Box 3, Folder 16-18)
  - Demidoff, Prince, circa 1846-1857; (2 folders) (Box 3, Folder 19-20)
  - Denison, I. E., circa 1854-1860 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - De Witt, William H., 1852-1853 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Dix, John A., 1843-1852 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Duncan, Lucius, 1847-1864 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Duncan, Mary, 1856-1858, 1867-1872; (2 folders) (Box 3, Folder 25-26)
  - Duppa, Bryan, 1844-1858 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Durant, Heloise, 1864-1867 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Dury, F. W., 1852-1873; (3 folders) (Box 3, Folder 29-31)
  - Dury, Louisa Gibson, 1848, 1861-1871; (2 folders) (Box 3, Folder 32-33)
  - D, Miscellaneous: Da, 1840-1865 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    Dalton, H. H.
    Dana, Edmund W.
    Davenport, D. G. A.
    Davis, Benjamin W.
    Davis, Gilbert
    Davis, H.
    Davis, J. P.
    Davis, N.
    Davis, Richard
  - D, Miscellaneous: De-Di, 1844-1868 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    De Boigne, Anna
    Del Monti, Marquis
    Dennistown, James
    Dexter, Mr.
    D'Hautville, Frederick Grand
    Di Centi, Jos.
    Dickens, Asbury
    Dickens, C. T.
    Dickens, Serace[?]
    Dixwell, J. J.
  - D, Miscellaneous: Do-Dr, 1851-1872 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    Doeg, William H.
    Douglas, Alfred
    Douglas, William
    Drake, James M.
    Draper, Ada A.
    Draper, Simeon
    Drinkwater, P. B.
  - D, Miscellaneous: Du, 1847-1873 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    Duckworth, William
    Du Fresne Bros.
    Dunlap, L.
    Dunn, W. H.
    Durand, Asher B.
    Duranty & Co.
    Duyckinck, George L.
    Dyke, Henry
  - Eaton, Charles J. M., 1845-1855; (5 folders) (Box 3, Folder 38-42)
  - Eaton, Charles J. M., 1856-1869; (3 folders) (Box 3, Folder 43-45)
  - Eckley, Sophie May, circa 1862 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Estcourt, J. Sothern, 1864-1865 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Evans, Thomas K., 1867-1869 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Everett, Edward, 1841-1846; (4 folders) (Box 3, Folder 49-52)
  - Everett, Edward, circa 1847-1850; (3 folders) (Box 3, Folder 53-55)
  - Everett, Edward, 1851-1855; (4 folders) (Box 4, Folder 1-4)
  - Everett, Edward, 1856-1858; (6 folders) (Box 4, Folder 5-10)
  - Everett, Edward, 1859-1862; (4 folders) (Box 4, Folder 11-14)
  - E, Miscellaneous: Ea-Ec, 1855-1868 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Earl, John O.
    Earl of Seafield
    Earl of Warwick
    Eastman, Susan S.
    Easton, Alfred H.
    Eaton, Amasu[?] M.
    Eaton, D. C.
    Eckley, D. (David)
  - E, Miscellaneous: Ed-Eg, 1845-1863 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    Eddy, C. W.
    Edgar, Miss L.
    Edwards, Alfred P.
    Edwards, Edward W.
    Edwards, I. M.
    Egerton, Lord F.
  - E, Miscellaneous: El-En, 1855-1872 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    Elder, Mr. & Mrs. J.
    Emerson, George T.
    Endicott, J. B.
    Engle, F.
  - Fairbairn, Peter, 1854-1856 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Fairbanks, Franklin, 1871-1873 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Findlay, W. L., 1854-1856 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Firth, Ida, 1865-1866 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Fish, Hamilton, 1857-1871; (3 folders) (Box 4, Folder 22-24)
  - Flagg, E. B., circa 1847-1853 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Franks, Edward, 1858-1859 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Freeman, Mr., 1848-1851 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Fuller, Charles F., 1855-1869 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - F, Miscellaneous: Fa-Fi, 1848-1873 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    Fairbanks, Henry
    Falaideau, Chevalier
    Falconer, W.
    Fallani, Sofia
    Fell, John A.
    Felton, C. C.
    Felton, L. B.
    Field, Henry M.
    Field, M. E.
    Field, Mrs. Marshall
    Field, Mary S.
    Field, Morris & Co.
  - F, Miscellaneous: Fl-Fo, 1849-1870 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    Flagg, E. B.
    Flash, Alexander
    Forbes, Alex
    Ford, Alfred E.
    Forshey, Caleb G.
    Foster, William Russell
    Fox, E. W.
  - F, Miscellaneous: Fr-Fu, 1845-1873 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    Frailey, Jas. Madison
    Franchi, Franco
    Franklin, Benjamin
    Franklin, D. Lewis
    Fred. Huth & Co.
    Freeman, A. W.
    Freeman, Florence
    French, A. J.
    French & Co.
    Fuller, Joseph W.
  - Gayarre, Charles, 1849-1852 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - German Bank of London, 1870-1871 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Gibson, Ann, 1819-1852; (5 folders) (Box 4, Folder 34-38)
  - Gibson, James, 1837-1860 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Gipner, C. Theodore, 1867-1870; (3 folders) (Box 4, Folder 40-42)
  - Goldsmith, Anne, 1866-1867 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Gooch, C. C., 1850, 1863-1865 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Gould, Walter, 1850-1855 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Gourdin, H., 1844-1857, 1866; (5 folders) (Box 4, Folder 46-50)
  - Graham, J. Lorimer, 1863-1864 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Grant, John, 1844-1870; (3 folders) (Box 4, Folder 52-54)
  - Gray, Henry Peters, 1850-1859 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Gray, John A. C., 1859-1871 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Green, Wharton J., 1858-1860 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Greenway, Edward M., 1845-1860 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Griswold, Charles, 1853-1865 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - G, Miscellaneous: Gab-Gal, 1837-1873 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Gabbitt, Harriett
    Gadsby, John
    Gadsby, Miss Julia
    Gaines, Edmund P.
    Gaines, Myra Clark
    Gaines, M. I.
    Gale, T. W.
    Gallagher, W. D.
    Gallico, Alex
    Gallier, C. M.
    Galt, P. H.
  - G, Miscellaneous: Gar-Gay, 1845-1873 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Gardenier, Mr.
    Gardiner, Frederic
    Gardner, C. E.
    Gardner, John L.
    Garner, Thomas
    Garvey, Richard
    Gatewood, W. C.
    Gayley, James M.
  - G, Miscellaneous: Ge, 1853-1871 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Gemmell[?], Mr.
    General Post Office, London
    Genin, John N.
    Gerry, Samuel L.
  - G, Miscellaneous: Gi, 1844-1870 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Gibson, Charles M.
    Gibson, Wood
    Gifford, J. G.
    Gilbert, Fred E.
    Gillespie, Alexander
    Gilmore, James
    Giorgi, David
    Giradot & Perdicary
  - G, Miscellaneous: Go, 1841-1872 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Godwin, N. B.
    Goldsmith, Alban
    Goldsmith, Anne
    Goodban, Edward
    Goodhue & Co.
    Goncet, M.
    Goranx, D.
    Gordon, Charles
    Gordon, George
    Gower, A. A.
  - G, Miscellaneous: Gra-Gre, 1837-1870 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Graberg, Eleanora
    Granger, F.
    Grant & Co.
    Graves, Mr.
    Great International Exhibition of 1862
    Greeley, Horace
    Green, Duff
    Green, Solomon
    Greene & Co.
    Greenleaf, May L.
    Greenough, Mrs.
    Grew, Henry Sturges
  - G, Miscellaneous: Gri, 1846-1856 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Griffin, William Preston
    Grilli, Ferd.
    Grimke, James M.
    Grindlay, R. Melville
    Griswold, George
  - G, Miscellaneous: Gu, 1841-1855 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Guione[?], Clement
    Guise, John W.
    Gurney, Russell
  - Haight, D. W., 1867-1873 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Hamilton, Allen, circa 1858-1862 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Harling, W. O., 1845-1872 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Harris, C. H., 1867-1868 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Harris, George, 1843-1848, 1858 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Healy, George P. A., 1849-1865 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Hennen, Duncan & Mrs., 1850-1856 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Hewins, Amos & Charles A. Hewins, 1853-1855 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Heyward, William, circa 1849-1859 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Hildreth, Arthur & Caroline Gould Hildreth, circa 1867, 1871 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Hills, Margaret M., circa 1864-1865 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Hoge, William, 1847-1852 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Hogg, William, 1872 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Holland, C. B., 1863-1866 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Holland, Robert, 1842-1846 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Holloway, M. M., 1852-1865; (3 folders) (Box 5, Folder 24-26)
  - Hooker, J. C., 1848-1858 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Horn, G. W., 1850-1860 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Hughes, George W., 1837-1847 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Hunnewell, James F., 1862-1863 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Hyde, Samuel T., 1860-1862 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - H, Miscellaneous: Had-Han, 1847-1872 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    Haden, Charles
    Hall, E. Edwin
    Hall, Frederic
    Hall, Helen
    Hall, Horace
    Hall, Orazio
    Hall, S. C.
    Hamilton, F. H.
    Hammond, T. A.
    Hampton, C. F.
    Hampton, Wade
    Hancock, Sol.
  - H, Miscellaneous: Har, 1841-1868 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    Hare, F. G.
    Harlan, A.
    Harris, I. Morrison
    Harrison, Gertrude
    Harrison, James H.
    Harrison, Joseph
    Harrison, Robert
    Hartman, Joseph
    Hartwill, Rubin Gerald
  - H, Miscellaneous: Has-Haz, 1838-1870 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    Hashard et Fils
    Hasty, Captain
    Hatch, Thomas B. R.
    Hautmann, Anton
    Hawley, D. Edwin
    Haworth, G. Fanny
    Hay, Sir Adam
    Haydon, Dudley M.
    Hays, Thomas
    Hayter, W. G.
    Hazard, Joseph P.
  - H, Miscellaneous: He-Hi, 1838-1871 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    Henking, Charles G.
    Henriques, Mrs.
    Herrick, M. A.
    Herring, Silas C.
    Hicks, Thomas
    Hibbert, F.
    Hildeburn Brothers & Co.
    Hinkley, John W.
    Hitchcock, Henry L.
    Hitz, John
  - H, Miscellaneous: Hod-Hoo, 1838-1876 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    Hodges, E. F.
    Hodgkinson, W. G.
    Hogan, John
    Hoge, James
    Hoit, A. G.
    Hoke, A.
    Holland, Lord
    Home, D. D.
    Homer, C. B.
    Honeywood, W.
    Hoodless, W. R.
    Hook, J. D. W.
    Hooper, R. C.
  - H, Miscellaneous: Hop-Hox, 1843-1873 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    Hope, S. P.
    Hopkins, Erastus
    Hopkins, Lewis S.
    Hosmer, Miss
    Howard, D. C. & E. F.
    Howard, Henry
    Howard, William Key
    Howland, R. S.
    Hoxie[?], T.
  - H, Miscellaneous: Hu-Hy, 1851-1872 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    Hudson, Eunice W.
    Huguet & Van Lint
    Hulbert, Milan
    Hunt, Genl. Menucan[?]
    Hunt, Thomas N.
    Hunter, Buckley & Co.
    Hurlbut, Mrs. A. P.
    Hyde, Linox[?]
    Hynes, W. R.
  - Ibbotson, Alfred and Louisa Powers Ibbotson (Ibbotson Brothers & Co.), 1859-1865; (5 folders) (Box 5, Folder 39-43)
  - Ibbotson, Alfred and Louisa Powers Ibbotson (Ibbotson Brothers & Co.), 1866-1873; (4 folders) (Box 5, Folder 44-47)
  - I, Miscellaneous, 1853-1873 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    Ibbotson, Henry J.
    Indio, Augusto
    Irvin, J. F.
    Isaac, John R.
    Izard, Allen S.
  - Jones, Samuel, 1854-1855, 1871 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Just, William, 1867-1872 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - J, Miscellaneous: Ja, 1835-1870 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    Jackson, Andrew
    Jackson & Graham
    Jackson, Herman
    Jackson, Jennie
    Jackson, J. M.
    Jackson Monument Committee
    James, Francis
    Janin, L.
    Jarves, J. J.
  - J, Miscellaneous: Jb-Jh, 1850-1866 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    J. Bulowe & Co.
    Jeannin, Louisa Anne
    Jennings, Isaac
    J. H. Ashbridge & Co.
    J. H. Brower & Co.
  - J, Miscellaneous: Joh, 1844-1873 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    Johnson, Carrie A.
    Johnson, H. D.
    Johnson, Isaac
    Johnson, Nellie
    Johnson, Marc
    Johnson, Mary A.
    Johnson, W. C.
    Johnson, Fry & Co.
    Johnston, James B.
  - J, Miscellaneous: Jon-Ju, 1853-1868 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    Jones, H. L.
    Jones, Jacob P.
    Jones, Owen
    Jones, S. L. B. & Helen S. J.
    Jones, T.
    Josephson, H.
    Josephson, J. F.
    Juder[?], Auguste
  - Kinney, William B. & E. Clementine Kinney, circa 1854-1865; (3 folders) (Box 5, Folder 55-57)
  - Kip, William Ingraham, 1846-1865 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - K, Miscellaneous: Ka-Ki, 1846-1870 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    Kasson, John A.
    Kay, W. F.
    Kelk, John
    Kennedy, Hiram
    Kenyon, John
    Kidder, H. P.
    Kimber, Thomas
    King, Charlotte E.
    King, Lizzie
    King, McMillan C.
    King, Rufus
    Kinney, E. C.
    Kirkup, S.[?]
    Kirn, H.
  - K, Miscellaneous: Kn-Ku, 1841-1870 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    Knight, William Fitzroy
    Koecker, Joseph D.
    Koslof, Marie
    Kublie, Alphonse
  - Lampson, C. M., 1864-1868 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Lamson, John, 1852 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Langdon, William Chauncey, 1857-1873 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Lanphier, W. H., 1849 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Latham, Milton S., 1867-1869; (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
  - Lawrence, Abbott, circa 1836-1852 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Lawrence, James, 1865-1870 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Leaf, William L., 1864-1868 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Lenox, James, 1851-1858; (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 6-7)
  - Lester, C. Edwards, 1844-1846 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Litchfield, Edwin C., 1864-1870; (3 folders) (Box 6, Folder 9-11)
  - Livezey, John, 1861 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Locke, J. L. & Laura I. Locke, circa 1849-1854 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - London & Ryder (W. H. Ryder), 1859-1863 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Long, William L., 1855-1864 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Longfellow, Samuel, 1870 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Low, Cornelius, 1842-1843 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Lowell, Charles, circa 1838-1843 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Loyd, Lewis, 1867-1868 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Lyman, E. H. R., 1869 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - L, Miscellaneous: Lam-Lat, 1844-1872 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    Lambeth, W. M.
    Lampronti, Paolo
    Lampson, Norman S.
    Latrobe, Jno. H. B.
  - L, Miscellaneous: Law, 1838-1870 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    Lawrence, F. B.
    Lawrence, Frank C.
    Lawrence, Katherine
    Lawrence, T. B.
  - L, Miscellaneous: Lb-Le, 1843-1870 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    L. B. Babcock & Co.
    Leather, Mr.
    Lee, Josephine D.
    Leeds, Henry H.
    Lenthall, Mary K.
    Leverick, C. P.
    Lewis, Winslow
  - L, Miscellaneous: Lh-Ll, 1839-1873 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    L'Hommedieu, Stephen
    Liggett, Julia
    Linton, David
    Lippincott, J. B.
    Lincoln, Lionel
    Little, A. A.
    Lloyd, John Whitlocke
    Lloyd, G. W.
  - L, Miscellaneous: Loc-Lon, 1851-1869 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    Lockwood, Julia
    London, D. H.
    Longfellow, H. W.
    Longworth, Nicolas
  - L, Miscellaneous: Lor-Low, 1850-1873 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    Lorant-Leghorn, D.
    Lorne, Marquis of
    Lothrop, Thornton
    Loubal[?], J. F.
    Louisiana, Governor & Sec. of State
    Low, David
    Low, Josiah O.
    Low, Samuel
    Lowry, William H.
  - L, Miscellaneous: Lu-Ly, 1854-1871 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    Ludlow, H.
    Ludlum, Sarah
    Luia[?], L. G.
    Luther, D.
    Lutwidge, C. R. Fletcher
    Lytton, R. R.
  - Mackie, John William, circa 1844-1847 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Macquay & Pakenham, 1845, 1851-1867; (3 folders) (Box 6, Folder 29-31)
  - Malchior, Alexander, 1849-1862 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Malenchini, Rocco, 1848-1850 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Marie, Peter, 1866-1867 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Marsh, George O., circa 1853-1857 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Marsh, George P., 1847-1870; (6 folders) (Box 6, Folder 36-41)
  - Marye, George T., 1860-1861 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Masi, Emilio, 1866-1871 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Maxey, Virgil, 1840-1844 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Maxwell, H. D., 1844-1854 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - McCord, Louisa, circa 1859-1870 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - McCracken, J. & R., 1843-1873; (3 folders) (Box 6, Folder 47-49)
  - McHenry, James H., 1845-1860 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - McLeod, Helen, circa 1856-1857 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Merriman, Oliver A., 1849-1852 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Miles, Mr., 1852-1857 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Miller, Andrew, 1850-1858; (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 54-55)
  - Mirandoli, N., 1848 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Moffatt, Dr. W. B., 1851-1868 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Morgan, J. S., 1856-1872; (3 folders) (Box 6, Folder 58-60)
  - Morgan, N. Denison, circa 1870-1873 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Morrill, Justin S., 1866-1873 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Morris, John B., 1852-1853 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Morris, William R., 1847-1851 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Murphy, Margaret S., 1866-1868 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - M, Miscellaneous: Mac, 1839-1870 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Macaulay, D.
    Macbean, William
    MacComb, Genl. A.
    MacDonald, Hercules
    MacDonald, James W.
    MacDonald, Laurence
    MacKay, Robert
    MacKay, William
    Mackworth, Digby
    Macleod, E.
    Macpherson, M. T.
  - M, Miscellaneous: Mal-Mar, 1845-1868 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Malcolm, J.
    Mallett, A. B.
    Mallett, E. J.
    Marcey, W. L.
    Marggraff, R.
    Mariotti, Lorenzo
    Markoe, Wilbur & Scott
    Marsh, Caroline C.
    Marsh, Susan
    Martin, Eugene
    Martin, George
    Martin, Mary
  - M, Miscellaneous: Mat-Mau, 1860-1872 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Mathews, Albert
    Mathews, L.
    Matthews, Arthur
    Mathini, Gevis.[?]
    Mattei, Francesco
    Mauck, Bligh
    Mauritz, Mr.
  - M, Miscellaneous: Mc, 1839-1870 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    McClennan, Charles S.
    McCreary, Mary J.
    McCurdy, Charles J. C.
    McDuffie, George
    McKay, David
    McKeane, Thomas
    McLain, R. T.
    McLean, N. C.
    McNab, John
  - M, Miscellaneous: Me, 1844-1870 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Mead, Larkin G.
    Meade, Mrs. M. C.
    Meigs, W. C.
    Mendsen, William F.
    Mercantile Library Association
    Mercer, Samuel
    Meline, Louis P.
    Messinger, Dan
    Metzger, Lodovico
  - M, Miscellaneous: Mi, 1846-1864 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Midre, G.
    Miles, William Porcher
    Miller, Charles E.
    Miller, John
    Miller, Lester
    Miller, William S.
    Mills, Edgar
    Mills, J. K.
    Mills, Lewis E.
    Mills, Margaret S.
    Mills, Robert
    Mitchell, Donald G.
  - M, Miscellaneous: Mon-Moo, 1845-1870 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Montalant[?], A. Martin
    Moore, Lucius
    Moore, Morris
    Moore, William C.
  - M, Miscellaneous: Mor, 1846-1872 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Morgan, George E.
    Morgan, Henry J.
    Moro, N. M.
    Morris, Clarence
    Morris, S. C.
    Morris, T. H.
    Morse, A. C.
    Morse, Samuel F. B.
  - M, Miscellaneous: Mos-Mu, 1856-1870 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Moss, A. A.
    Mottasse, George S.
    Mozier, J.
    Munroe, J.
    Murdock, Mary E.
    Murray, A. M.
  - Naesmyth, John M., circa 1863-1870; (2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 12-13)
  - Nash, Joshua, 1848-1855 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Nicholson, Samuel, 1863-1870 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Niemann, Edmund, 1860-1862; (2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 16-17)
  - Nourse & Co. (Michael Nourse), 1855 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - N, Miscellaneous: Na, 1840-1870 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    Naden[?], Charles
    Naylor, Bunyon[?], & Co.
    Neagle, John
    Neill, Samuel M.
    Nevins, J. West
    Newhauser, Mr.
    New Orleans Times
  - N, Miscellaneous: Ni, 1852-1871 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    Nichols, James R.
    Nichols, W.
    Niles, H. T.
    Niles, W. W.
    Nist, J. P.
  - N, Miscellaneous: No-Ny, 1843-1868 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    Noble, James
    Noccioli, Carlo
    Northcote, C. A.
    Norton, Brinsley
    Norton, Charles Eliot
    Norton, Frank
    Norton, James S.
    Norton, John
    Nott, J. C.
    Notti, Mr.
    Nourse, Hiram
    Nye, Gideon
  - Ombrosi, James, 1849-1850 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - O, Miscellaneous, 1847-1866 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    Ogden, W. H.
    Ohio Life Insurance & Trust Co.
    Oldfield, Edmund
    Oldham, Helen
    Olmstead, Lemuel G.
    Ostinelli, Luigi
    Otley, Charles
    Overstone, Lord
    Owen & Clark
  - Packer, Harriet S., 1868-1870 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Page, Mrs. B., 1856-1858 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Parker, John, 1841-1843 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Peabody, Francis, 1845-1849 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Peabody, George, 1846-1864; (5 folders) (Box 7, Folder 28-32)
  - Penniman, James F., 1851-1857 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Perkins, George R., 1869-1875 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Phillips, S. C., 1837-1846 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Pickens, F. W., 1837-1857 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Pitman, John T., 1857-1860; (3 folders) (Box 7, Folder 37-39)
  - Playfair, James, circa 1845-1850; (2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 40-41)
  - Powers, Benjamin, 1831-1860; (5 folders) (Box 7, Folder 42-46)
  - Powers, Catherine, 1835, 1854-1870; (2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 47-48)
  - Powers, Elizabeth Gibson, circa 1832, 1834-1836; (6 folders) (Box 7, Folder 49-54)
  - Powers, Elizabeth Gibson, 1837; (4 folders) (Box 7, Folder 55-58)
  - Powers, Elizabeth Gibson, 1848-1857 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Powers, Longworth, 1851-1859; (3 folders) (Box 8, Folder 2-4)
  - Powers, Philander, 1827-1834 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Powers, Preston, 1865-1868 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Powers, Sampson, 1836-1853; (4 folders) (Box 8, Folder 7-10)
  - Powers, Sampson, 1854-1869; (3 folders) (Box 8, Folder 11-13)
  - Powers Family, Miscellaneous: A-Z, 1831-1871; (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 14-15)
  - Prall, Margaret A., circa 1850 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Prescott, T. O., 1848-1852 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Preston, John S., circa 1836-1861; (3 folders) (Box 8, Folder 18-20)
  - Preston, William C., circa 1836-1852 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Price, George W., 1859-1864 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Prime, Frederick, 1848-1849, 1866 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - P, Miscellaneous: Pag-Pap, 1854-1870 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    Paget, Lady
    Paige, J. W.
    Paine, Jno. W.
    Palmer, Erastus D.
    Palmerini, Ferdinando
    Papi, Clemente
  - P, Miscellaneous: Par-Pay, 1844-1873 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    Parish, Henry
    Park, Anna C.
    Parker, James
    Parkman, J.
    Parmele, Edward
    Parsons, T. W.
    Pate & Sons
    Patten, D.
    Patterson, William L.
    Pattison, Delia
    Payer, Raffael
    Payne, Daniel C.
    Paynter, Fanny
  - P, Miscellaneous: Pe, 1836-1862 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    Peabody, Joseph
    Peacoke, Edward
    Pearce, Stephen
    Peck, Jud
    Pelham, Charles P.
    Pennock, Barclay
    Perkins, Charles C.
    Perkins, F. D.
    Perkins, Stephen
    Petrini, Ruggero
  - P, Miscellaneous: Ph-Po, 1846-1872 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    Phillip, J. Boisin[?]
    Pierce, Mr.
    Pierpont, John
    Place, E. B.
    Plowden, Mr.